agilemarks.com 2011-09-24

# Interesting News, Interesting Articles, Interesting Videos › Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

**Our Team at AgileMarks is Proud of always Continuation our Strict Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy states the Following -**

 **

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

This policy covers how we use your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information.

Any personal information received will only be used to fill your diplomacy. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone.

1\. Your Information Is Kept Confidential – Any information you give us while signing up for our Mailings or using any Service on our network that requires your information such as Name, email take up, etc. will be kept confidential.

2\. We involuntarily send you our bi-weekly ezine when you subscribe to any service on our network which requires your email take up. You can unsubscribe from the same anytime.

3\. You will not be shown any Racial Content or Discriminatory Material without Adult Content.

4\. No Cheating – We will not cheat with You while offering you the Best Services on the internet.

5\. At the end of the day, we are ranked as one of the most reputed website networks online. We be going to to keep it that way.

**

**6\. Rest assured, your privacy is of greatest importance to us, as always.**
